So we figured out the dates you've got the receptionist to understand when you want to stay how long
所以我们算出了你让接待员了解你想待多久的日期
you want to stay.
你想留下来。
How many people go.
多少人去。
Now we need to get into the different room types.
现在我们需要进入不同的房间类型。
And there are many different room types for different hotels.
而且不同的酒店有很多不同的房型。
Obviously we can't cover all of them we're going to try to get into them a little bit.
显然，我们无法涵盖所有​​这些，我们将尝试深入了解它们。
Sure.
当然。
The last thing that was said was me and my wife.
最后说的是我和我的妻子。
Right.
正确的。
Who's staying.
谁留下来。
Me and my wife.
我和我的妻子。
That's two people.
那是两个人。
Sure.
当然。
This is just to acknowledge something.
这只是承认一些事情。
This is a very very useful word to say.
这是一个非常非常有用的词。
Yes.
是的。
Hey can I can I go I need to I need to finish something.
嘿，我可以去吗？我需要我需要完成一些事情。
Yeah sure.
好，当然。
OK.
好的。
Or to confirm that you've got information.
或者确认你有信息。
I have to leave tomorrow at 3:00 p.m..
我必须在明天下午 3:00 离开。
OK.
好的。
Sure sure.
一定一定。
That could mean I understand.
那可能意味着我明白了。
Yes.
是的。
Or it could also mean I recognize that you said that I understand.
或者这也可能意味着我承认你说我理解。
And if you tell me that tomorrow I will remember it probably.
如果你告诉我明天我可能会记得。
All right.
好的。
Sure.
当然。
And which room type would you like.
以及您喜欢哪种房型。
Which room type would you like.
您想要哪种房型。
Could you tell me more about your room types.
你能告诉我更多关于你的房间类型吗？
Maybe I've never stayed at the villa hotel before.
也许我以前从未住过别墅酒店。
So I need to know more.
所以我需要知道更多。
We have a standard room standard is often described as the basic option of something the basic option.
我们有标准间的标准常常被描述为一些基本选项的基本选项。
So if you get a car with standard features that means it doesn't have anything extra.
因此，如果您购买的是具有标准功能的汽车，则意味着它没有任何额外功能。
It's kind of the basic thing.
这是一种基本的东西。
And there's nothing about it that's maybe premium premium premium has that's an IOU and premium has
没有什么可能是溢价 溢价 溢价 是借据 溢价
lots of extra things with a standard room which has two double beds two double beds.
标准间有很多额外的东西，有两张双人床和两张双人床。
That's one hundred and twenty seven dollars per night.
那是每晚一百二十七美元。
OK.
好的。
Notice that when we read this we don't say dollar 127.
请注意，当我们阅读本文时，我们不会说 127 美元。
We say one hundred and twenty seven and then we say dollars OK even though it's before even though the
我们说 127 然后我们说美元 OK 即使是之前
dollar sign is before.
美元符号是之前。
That's one hundred and twenty seven dollars per night.
那是每晚一百二十七美元。
Then we also have a queen room which is 140 but the room is the same size to the Queen room has a queen
然后我们还有一个140的大床房，但房间和大床房一样大，有一个大床房
bed.
床。
The bed size is Queen general sizes for beds in hotels are double.
床的尺寸是大床，酒店的床一般尺寸是双倍的。
And then Queen and then King and this is in order of size sometimes you'll see a twin bed twin is generally
然后是女王，然后是国王，这是按大小排列的，有时你会看到一张双人床
smaller.
更小。
So twin is one person but you don't usually see that in a hotel.
所以双胞胎是一个人，但你通常不会在酒店看到它。
You'll see double queen and king.
你会看到双王后和国王。
OK.
好的。
So the next one but the room is the same size the deluxe room deluxe is a word that's used to describe
所以下一个但是房间大小一样dluxe room deluxe是用来形容的词
something that does have extra sometimes premium things added onto it.
有些东西确实有额外的，有时是额外的东西添加到它上面。
If you go to a fast food restaurant and you get something that has extra it's often a deluxe.
如果你去一家快餐店，你会得到一些额外的东西，那通常是豪华的。
For example a deluxe burger.
例如豪华汉堡。
There are extra things on the burger the deluxe room has a king bed and the room is bigger.
汉堡上还有额外的东西，豪华房有一张特大号床，房间更大。
That's one hundred and eighty dollars.
那是一百八十美元。
Notice I say a hundred and eighty dollars not one hundred and eighty.
注意我说的是一百八十美元而不是一百八十美元。
You don't have to say one we often say oh if it's anything that is one an hour a day a year a month.
你不必说一个我们经常说的哦，如果它是一年一个月一天一小时的任何事情。
A hundred.
一百。
That's one hundred and eighty dollars per night then of course we have the suite which has a separate
那是每晚一百八十美元那么当然我们有套房，其中有一个单独的
bedroom a big balcony and a Jacuzzi a balcony is basically an outside an outdoor area.
卧室一个大阳台和一个按摩浴缸一个阳台基本上是一个户外区域。
Building is here and then there's a balcony that comes out like that.
建筑物在这里，然后有一个像那样出来的阳台。
It's a very ugly balcony.
这是一个非常丑陋的阳台。
And not every hotel room has one.
并不是每个酒店房间都有一个。
So that's a nice that's a kind of a deluxe thing right suite room is usually the nicest room in the
所以这是一个很好的那种豪华的东西右套房通常是最好的房间
hotel and a Jacuzzi.
酒店和按摩浴缸。
Wow a Jacuzzi is often called a hot tub hot tub.
哇，按摩浴缸通常被称为热水浴缸热水浴缸。
And this is kind of like a a bathtub.
这有点像浴缸。
But it's more a public thing that multiple people can share and it's not actually for bathing it's for
但它更像是一个多人可以共享的公共事物，它实际上不是为了洗澡而是为了
relaxation.
松弛。
And it bubbles it's hot.
它冒泡它很热。
It's got jets of water.
它有水柱。
It's called a Jacuzzi or a hot tub.
它被称为按摩浴缸或热水浴缸。
So this is a very nice room.
所以这是一个非常好的房间。
OK.
好的。
Now we have to decide which of these rooms we want.
现在我们必须决定我们想要哪些房间。
We have the standard which is the basic.
我们有基本的标准。
We have the Queen.
我们有女王。
We have the deluxe and we also have the suite room.
我们有豪华房，也有套房。
Which one are we going to pick.
我们要选择哪一个。